A Guide to the L. T. Christian Funeral Home Records, 1912-1986
Library of Virginia
- Stevenson, Olga Frederickson, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Stewart, Annie C., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Stewart, Avis Barney, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Stewart, F. Spottswood, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Stilling, Harry Benning, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Stine, David Josiah, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Stine, George Oliver, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Stine, Gregory Niles [infant], 1952 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Stine, Lynn Berkley, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Stine, Mary Kretzer, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Stines, Joseph L., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Stinespring, Emmett Noel, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Stipe, Edith May, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Stirling, Jean Richmond, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Stirton, James William, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Stockdell, Barbara Barker, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Stockdell, Georgeanna Watts, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Stockdell, Helen, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Stockdell, Mary M., 1986 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Stockton, Sallie, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Stogner, Feral Tucker, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Stokes, Douglas Galloway, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Stokes, Joseph H., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Stokes, Libbie Keener, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Stokes, Lillian Ashby, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Stokes, Lucy Hayes, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Stokes, Margaret Pickett, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Stokes, Thomas D., 1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Stone, Grover C., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Stone, Iredell Johnson, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Stone, James H., 1974 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Stone, Josephine H., 1958 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Stone, Marian Lecky, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Stone, Pattie J., 1932 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Stone, Robert Leaky, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Stoner, Ione Cutler, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Stoner, Walter E., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Stork, Grace Helen, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Storrs, Addie Sue Payne, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Storrs, Elizabeth Johnstone, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Storrs, Harvey Fox, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Storrs, Mary D. Fox, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Storrs, Robert Williamson, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Storrs, Robert Williamson, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Stover, Mildred, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Strader, Thomas Arnold, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Stratton, Nora, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Strauss, Charles Edward, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Strauss, Clara Louise, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Strauss, Gabriel L., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Strauss, Lewis S., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Strauss, Rosa Lichtenstein, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Street, Abbot Prince, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Street, Florence Prince, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Street, Frances Elizabeth, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Street, George L., Jr., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Street, John Robert, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Street, Virginia Lee, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Street, Walter Newbill, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Street, William Henry, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Streett, Mal Greene, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Stribling, Eva Croxton, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Stribling, James Hunter, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Strickland, Julie Ann, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Strickland, Mary, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Stringfellow, Elizabeth Hargrave, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Strother, Alfred T., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Strother, Bryant L., 1981 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Strother, Bryant Leitch, Jr., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Strother, Evelyn Richardson, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Strother, James French, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Strother, Lucy Mordecai, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Strother, Mary E., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Strother, Morgan William, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Strother, Rosa, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Strother, William Fuqua, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Stuart, Harry C., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Stubbs, Sarah Marguerite, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Stublett, Alice M., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Stubs, John Anderson, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Stuckey, Mabel L., 1927 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Sublett, Lottie Lucy, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Sublett, Lucille C., 1981 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Sublett, Thomas Clemmitt, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Suggs, Grace Lorraine, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Suggs, William D., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Suggs, William Durwood, III, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Sullivan, Edna G. Turner, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Sullivan, Joseph C., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Sullivan, Lawrence Clifton, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Sullivan, Thomas Melti., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Summers, Flora, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Summey, Jane Frances, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Summey, Thomas Johnson, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Sutherland, Eva Eugenia, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Sutherland, Jean Renee, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Sutherland, Ruth P., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Sutherland, Wellford Ross, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Sutton, Amanda, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Sutton, Ella Wagner, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Sutton, Granville G., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Sutton, Henry Carroll, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Sutton, Herbert B., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Sutton, Hubert T., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Sutton, Lee Edwards, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Sutton, Lee Edwards, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Sutton, Lucy Byrd, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Sutton, Lula L., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Sutton, Mary Lucke, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Sutton, Morris Covington, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Sutton, Ruth Rogan McClellan, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Sutton, Sadie G., 1958 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Sutton, Wyndham Madison, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Swain, Sarah A., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Swann, Frances Dew, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Swann, Frances M., 1980 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Swanson, Claude A., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Sweeny, James, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Sweeny, Maurice J., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Sweeny, Ola Virginia, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Swift, Betty Dew Gregory, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Swift, Carter Gregory, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Switzer, Georgia Anna, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Switzer, Stella Marguerite Perkins, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Sydenstricker, A. H. Fitzhugh, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Sydnor, Alice Flash, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Sydnor, Ann Maria, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Sydnor, Eugene B., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Sydnor, M. Virginia, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Sydnor, S. Dorsey, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Sydnor, Sallie Bell W., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Sydnor, Sallie Dorsey, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Sydnor, Wilburn Lee, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Synon, John James, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Synon, Margaret, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Tabb, Bettie Harrison, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Tabb, Braxton Harrison, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Tabb, Cabell Mayo, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Tabb, Charles Brock, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Tabb, Edward Armstead, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Tabb, Frances May, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Tabb, Gay Lewis, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Tabb, Jeff M. J., 1925 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Tabb, John Floyd, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Tabb, Marguerite Ashley, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Tabb, Mary Perrin, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Tabb, Mary Susan B., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Tabb, Robert Cabell, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Tabb, Susan Garnett, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Tabb, Thomas Garnett, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Tabb, Thomas Garnett, Jr., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Tabb, Virginia Underwood, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Talbert, [infant] child of Richard Talbert, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Talbot, Aurelia Hall, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Talbott, Casandra Brown, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Talbott, Elizabeth Radford, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Talbott, Harry F., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Talbott, Wray Knight, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Talcott, Eva Carrington, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Talcott, Harriett R., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Talcott, Jennie McPhail, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Talcott, Liesa Archer, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Talcott, Maria Curtis Cocke, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Talcott, Mary Gray, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Taliaferro, Edith Peyton, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Taliaferro, Margaret W., 1974 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Talley, Anna Russell S. T., 1980 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Talley, Anne Myers, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Talley, Annie Pleasants, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Talley, Annie Wortham, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Talley, Daniel D., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Talley, Edmund Waddill, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Talley, Florence Bryan, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Talley, James Crump, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Talley, Leonora Waddill, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Talley, Mary Christian, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Talley, Minnie Saxby, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Talley, Nathaniel C., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Talley, William W., Jr., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Tallman, Bertie Lawson, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Talman, Marie F., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Tanner, Albert S., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Tanner, Eugene Sheldon, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Tanner, Ophelia Minor, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Tanner, Pattie B., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Tardy, Elizabeth Louise, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Tardy, Milton Ewing, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Tate, [Miss], 1941 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Tate, Joseph Allen, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Tate, Marion Sampson, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Tatum, George Marvin, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Tatum, Louise B., 1958 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Tatum, Mamie H., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Tatum, Mary Selden, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Taurman, Evelyn Taliaferro, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Taurman, Lewis Coleman, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Taurman, Mary Lawrence, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Taurman, Miriam Alma, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Taylor, Annie Cofield, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Taylor, Augusta Bruce, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Taylor, Bertha Decker, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Taylor, Bessie Tench, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Taylor, Blanche Lee, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Taylor, Byrd Warwick, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Taylor, Charles Alexander, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Taylor, Charles Frances, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Taylor, Charles G., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Taylor, Charles Marshall, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Taylor, Chester L., 1939 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Taylor, Cornelia Stone, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Taylor, Dalton, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Taylor, Dora A., 1969 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Taylor, Douglas Edwin, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Taylor, Edgar D., 1928 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Taylor, Edgar Nemon, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Taylor, Edith Palmer, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Taylor, Edwin Harvie, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Taylor, Elizabeth Horner Knox, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Taylor, Elsie Shepherd, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Taylor, Emma Scott, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Taylor, Ernest Miles, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Taylor, Ethel Gardner, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Taylor, Fannie Moncure, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Taylor, Floyd Brown, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Taylor, Francis Adams, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Taylor, Frank Davis, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Taylor, Garland Burnley, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Taylor, Garland Burnley, 1946 (disinterred) (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Taylor, George Broxton, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Taylor, George Keith, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Taylor, George M., Jr., n. d. (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Taylor, H. Richie, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Taylor, Helen Gray, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Taylor, Helen Keim, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Taylor, Henry Cox, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Taylor, Henry L., 1961 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Taylor, Henry Magruder, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Taylor, Henry Magruder, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Taylor, Henry P., 1976 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Taylor, Henry, Jr., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Taylor, Herbert Vidal, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Taylor, Herbert Watson, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Taylor, Hyman W., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Taylor, Irene Mildred, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Taylor, Jacquelin P., 1950 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Taylor, James Marshall, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Taylor, James Winston, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Taylor, Jaquelin E., 1985 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Taylor, Jessie James, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Taylor, Katherine James Christian, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Taylor, Katherine Wall, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Taylor, Lewis Harvie, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Taylor, Louis Benjamin, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Taylor, Lucy Macgruder, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Taylor, Lula Virginia Scott, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Taylor, Mable Stultz, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Taylor, Marion Pope, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Taylor, Martha Watson, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Taylor, Mary C., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Taylor, Mary Edmonds, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Taylor, Mary Gillespie, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Taylor, Mary Page, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Taylor, Mattie Bowles, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Taylor, Mildred Powell B., 1981 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Taylor, Nancy Brinton, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Taylor, Nettie, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Taylor, Paula Kay, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Taylor, Rhoda Davis, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Taylor, Richard C., 1975 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Taylor, Richard Field, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Taylor, Robert Lee, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Taylor, Robert Marshall, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Taylor, Rose Bauer, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Taylor, Ruth Baker, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Taylor, Ruth G., 1983 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Taylor, Sallie Floyd Brown, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Taylor, Sallie Smith, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Taylor, Sally Frances, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Taylor, Santley Marshall, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Taylor, Stuart A., 1958 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Taylor, Sue Powers, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Taylor, Virginia Bagby, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Taylor, Virginia Clarke, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Taylor, W. M., 1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Taylor, Walter Robert, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Taylor, Zachary L., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Teal, Charles Schlager, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Temple, John Towhig, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Temple, Thomas Brown, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Templeman, Samuel H., 1944 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Templeton, Martha Warlow, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Tener, Wallis McDonnell, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Tennant, Mary Newton Williams, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Tennant, Tilton, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Tennant, William Brydon, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Tenser, Edmonia E., 1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Terrell, Alma J., 1954 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Terrell, Erma Lambert, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Terrell, Mahlon Guest, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Terrell, Rosa B., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Terrell, William Amonette, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Terry, [infant] daughter of Daniel F., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Teusler, Mary Woodward, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Thabet, Frederick Joseph, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Thacker, Frank Howard, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Thaxton, Ada Crowdis, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Thaxton, George D., 1956 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Thaxton, Jordon Reese, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Thaxton, Maynie Reese, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Thayer, Mable Earlyn, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Thayer, Marjorie, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Thayer, May Breeden, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Thayer, Nelson Browning, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Thiem, Bertha Willis, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Thiermann, Nannie T., 1970 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Thom, John Phillip, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Thom, Martha W., 1930 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Thomas, [infant] son of William B., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Thomas, Alberta H., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Thomas, Annie Estell, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Thomas, Camp Tunis, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Thomas, Charles Herbert, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Thomas, Evalyn Stribling, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Thomas, Floyd Anderson, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Thomas, Glen Carlyton, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Thomas, Grace Ewan, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Thomas, Ina, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Thomas, India Watson, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Thomas, John R., 1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Thomas, Joseph Irving, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Thomas, Julian Pendleton, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Thomas, Lamar Curry, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Thomas, Lelia Booker, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Thomas, Lucian Betts, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Thomas, Marguerette, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Thomas, Pearl Tucker, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Thomas, Russell Edgar, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Thomas, Sue Doswell, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Thomas, Warner Maurice, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Thomas, Warwick, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Thomas, Willie Anna, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Thomason, Edwin B., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Thomason, Emily S., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Thomason, Luly Emma, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Thomason, Margaret Eugenia, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Thomason, Nancy Watson, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Thomasson, Emma Golson, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Thompson, Alice Hurt, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Thompson, Anne Claiborne, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Thompson, Annie Leona Mays, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Thompson, Catherine McLearen, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Thompson, Clara Louise, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Thompson, Drury P., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Thompson, Edna Elizabeth, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Thompson, Emma Cheatham, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Thompson, Fannie Elizabeth, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Thompson, Garnett Douglas, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Thompson, Guy Frank, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Thompson, Harriett Burke, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Thompson, Harry Clark, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Thompson, Helen Beall, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Thompson, Ida Fendrick, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Thompson, James Clarke (disinterment, see Thad T. Thompson), 1947 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Thompson, James Montgomery, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Thompson, Lilian Farrar, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Thompson, Luna N., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Thompson, Mae Alice Hurt (disinterment, see Thad T. Thompson), 1947 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Thompson, Mary M., 1981 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Thompson, Mary Virginia C., 1967 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Thompson, Matthew Christie, III [infant], 1960 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Thompson, Nash Hercules [infant], 1948 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Thompson, Ruth Ellen, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Thompson, Sallie Bond, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Thompson, Thad T. (disinterment), 1947 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Thompson, William Ernest, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Thompson, William McIlwaine, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Thompson, William Taliaferro, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Thompson, Willie Francis, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Thornton, A. H., 1935 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Thornton, Daniel McCarty Fitzhugh, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Thornton, Ellen Flournoy, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Thornton, James M., 1983 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Thornton, Marjorie Jones (see A. H. Thornton), 1946 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Thornton, Parke Poindexter, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Thornton, Robert James, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Thornton, Saide Elizabeth, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Thrall, Curtis Warner, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Thrall, Curtis Warner, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Thraves, Martha Catherine, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Thraves, William V., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Threadcraft, Hal Law, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Threadcraft, Katharine Prentiss, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Thurston, Sarah B., 1938 (interment of cremains, 1965) (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Thurston, Virginia Hughes, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Thurston, William Purcell, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Tibbetts, Maxie Hart, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Tice, Edith Fletcher, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Tilghman, Henry Granville, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Tilghman, Katherine S., 1969 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Tiller, Carolyn Best, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Tiller, Percy L., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Timberlake, Annie Catherine Kunker, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Timberlake, James Estes, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Tinsley, Emily Sallie, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Tinsley, Preston Fletcher, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Tinsley, Thomas Garland, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Todd, [infant], 1944 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Todd, Cecil Boyd, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Todd, Mary Powers, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Todd, Ruth Corbin, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Tolson, Francis Bowie, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Tolson, Sallie Bridges, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Tompkins, Ann Harrison, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Tompkins, Delia Patteson, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Tompkins, Elizabeth Nelson, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Tompkins, Ellen Wilkins, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Tompkins, Evelyn, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Tompkins, George Harry, Jr., 1944 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Tompkins, William Rouston, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Toms, Zach, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Toney, Robert Madison, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Torrence, Dorothy Wells, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Torrence, Elizabeth Green N., 1969 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Torrence, William Clayton, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Totten, Thomas Roach, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Tottle, John Walter, Jr., 1984 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Totty, Avis Hillsman, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Tounsley, Ida Chaplin F., 1967 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Towers, A. R., (wedding car service for daughter, 1952) (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Towles, Clarence Spottswood, Jr., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Townes, Laura Van Zant, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Townsend, Henry James, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Tracy, James H., Jr., 1953 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Tracy, Mabel E., 1952 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Trader, Marie Louise, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Trafford, Annie T., 1966 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Traine, Max, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Trammell, William Lee, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Trapnell, Mary D., 1980 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Trapnell, Nicholas McLean, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Travis, Presley L., 1963 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Traylor, Annie Gavin, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Traylor, Mary Garvin, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Traynham, Lucy Lipscomb Carter, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Tredway, William Chasteen, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Treibley, Susan Marie, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Trevillian, Harold Dudley, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Trexler, Robert William, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Trice, Ernest T., 1955 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Trice, Evangeline Palmer, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Trice, Everett Tucker, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Trice, Franklin A., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Trigg, Edward H., 1975 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Trigg, Emma Gray, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Trigg, Martha Boxley, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Trigg, Roberta, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Trigg, Roberta Hanewinckel, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Trimble, Dennis O. (2 folders), 1977 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Trimmer, Bessie S., 1972 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Trimmer, Samuel Julian, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Tritton, Robert Craige, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Troxell, Harry Schraden, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Tsimpidis, William, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Tucker, Alice Vernella, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Tucker, Ella Granberry, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Tucker, Emma Lee Barker, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Tucker, Etta Catlin, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Tucker, Florence McCallum, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Tucker, Frank Leslie, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Tucker, Harry C., 1938 (disinterred 1964) (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Tucker, Henry St. George, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Tucker, Howard, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Tucker, Hugh C. (also see oversize item), 1956 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Tucker, Janie Walsh, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Tucker, John Randolph, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Tucker, Laura V., 1965 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Tucker, Lillian Warnock, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Tucker, Madge Fife, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Tucker, Maria Elizabeth, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 29)